The GUNSAN Channel has begun!
Last time we made fireworks for our Manakata Festival.
We created a fireworks display
Craftsman sitting down.
That's right.
Actually making fireworks.
Gyuu
Here we go!
Gyuu.
How does the bridge look like?
Will it be a beautiful circle?
Ready!
Red button!
I knew I should have commented on it.
Ai-chan's
Fireworks!
I saw them again and they were really good!
I don't know... that time I was so excited...
I'm so sad.
I'm going.
Okay.
Okay!
Yum!
Yay!
Yum! Yum!
Yum, yum, yum.
Maybe not next time.
Maybe not.I might not be able to.
I'm sorry, but he went.
That's right, Mr. Fujimoto isn't here today.
He's not here.
He smelled bad last time.
That's true.
I think we're in trouble.
Let's go.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
It's kind of the same.
Ah, how are you?
Safe active duty.
Oh, by the way, Rico's jacket, too.
I've heard a lot about it.
This time?
Usually with short sleeves.
Some people are a little crazy.
I get that a lot.
It was black and white that day.
Yes, it was.
Love is green.
Pictures.
I have a lot of purses.
I have a wallet, but I can't carry it.
I pretended I didn't have one.
It's not like that.
It's not like that.No, it's not like that.
I was wondering if you could help me out a little bit. So... last time we had the fireworks here... that play...
The play... the fireworks... was the result of a competition... and we were awarded a prize.
We produced the first 4 minutes of the show... or maybe a whole song.
I'm sure it's great that we're going to produce a song for the first 4 minutes or a whole song.
I'm glad to hear that, because I don't know if I'll be able to launch it or not.
I'm glad you said I can produce a song to go with it.
I'm glad you told me I could produce the song.
Two eyes
Hey...
I have an image of that flower.
I've got an image of a flower, but I'd like to show you the bottom corner too.
I'm in the shape of a blouse that's been stood up and I saw it at home in the lyrics
I've got it
I'm sure it's there, isn't it? I feel like I'm singing.
Yes, yes, I'm really into it, but if I'm going to give it to you here, I'm only going to give it to you here
I think I'll just leave it at that.
I'd like to discuss with you all what kind of fireworks we should display to the lyrics of "This Port" today.
I'd like to discuss with you all what kind of fireworks we should display to the lyrics of the song.
And this time... with the students...
Oh!
No, no, no... you're filming here.
It doesn't make sense for us to think about it ourselves.
We'll work with the students to decide what kind of fireworks we're going to set off at the port.
We'll decide what kind of fireworks we'd like to display at our port.
Let's go.
This way?
No cracks!
Congratulations.
Thank you for watching.Thank you for watching!
Now let's take a look at the music video for "Corner Minato".
I hope the music video will give you an idea of the colors and shapes that would be appropriate for the lyrics.
I hope you can get an idea of what I'm talking about.
Thank you.
Sei, please switch on.
Seino
Switch on
ON
on
He's so cute.
Isn't it?
They all fit.
So cute.
So unique.
Love to love to love
by H.
I'm so happy with the image.
Puffed up.
There were some nods that seemed to be quite full.
I don't think you could see the expressions on the students' faces because you two were on the same side.
But I could see the expressions on the students' faces.
I'm looking forward to seeing it.
It was like the fireworks were just floating around.
I'm really looking forward to it.
Now let's think together about what kind of fireworks would be good with what kind of lyrics.
Ahhh...
Fireworks fireworks
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching!
Shall I write one line at a time? I'm writing lyrics now.
Is the sentence in blue?
That's nice.
You're really coming along there, too.
Love is a heart.
That's true.
That's great.
Damn heart.
Air division.
Like blue and green.
That's great.
More and more than us,
So it's like, let's put blue and green around here.
Ai-chan's batten.
You are going to put this much in?
Yes, that's what we did.
There were only three fireworks we made,
I made the red button, the most orthodox one,
The most orthodox one, a normal round one.
And Ai-chan has a batten.
Ai-chan has a batten and Ai-chan has a green one.
Green and a batten.
I don't know if I did it right.
There is a possibility that I'm not very good at it.
One more thing,
I'm not feeling too depressed today,
Ai Fujimoto, the guy who made this,
I made it,
I made it, I made it,
It's something like this, from Dragon Ball,
It's the shape of the "Dragon Ball".
It's the shape of a "Dragon Ball". I had one more shot,
I'm not sure if it's working or not, but I'm not sure if it's working or not.
I don't know if it's working or not,
I'm not sure if it's working or not, but I was thinking of adding those three shots.
It's hard to do that, isn't it?
I'm wondering if there's anything that looks like a bicycle? Fireworks.
What do you think? It looks like a bicycle.
It's cute.
Senrin.
Give me a name that sounds like a bicycle.
Okay, let's just call it Senlin.
I like it. Is it this one?
I think I know a girl who can get it right the first time.
Senlin.
Monster Ghost.
Nico.
Nico around here.
Nice.
Around here.
First of all, there's something like "Oh!", right?
Oh, yes. It's the intro.
Then the members say it.
I'm going to say it all at once from the members.
Only the members can do it.
Finish it up.
It's cute.
I'm wearing it with a member's mesher.I'm wearing it with a member's mesher.
I don't know what color it is.
I like it with yellow.
Oh, combination? Yellow and red.
But if it's red and green, it's Christmas.
Red and green, right? It's Christmas.
Purple and pink is cute.
Wow, you went that far.
When it comes to fireworks, you won't even know what color they are, will you? Purple and pink.
That's true. I can see through it.
Opposite colors. Opposite colors.
I can see that. But blue and yellow are cute.
I think blue and yellow are good.
Blue and yellow are good.
Next.
What's that look like?
Just roll.
I'd like to say four.
Oh, you want to launch Rico? You want it to reach here?
That's a good idea. Sure.
Okay, Riko's fireworks... right here.
But let's use the cross ones, just to make it easier.
I'm not bothered.
Me?
Ai-chan's fireworks...
Ai-chan's fireworks.
And Mr. Fujimoto, yes, indeed.
Fujimoto-san's horse dreo is your biggest worry.
Yes, he's the most nervous. He's made so many mistakes.
Like this?You do this?
Yeah, I'm trying to make them fit together.
I think I've done it two or three times, so I'm probably messing it up.
And I think the dragon is probably a better shape.
I think he's making a Dragon Ball with a circle and four stars.
I'll think about it, and then I'll move on.
Okay.
Rust.
This is...
Who?
Willow, willow, willow.
Willow...
I'll ask you once.
The colorful one.
Blue mambushi.
The black bowl, the flower seedlings
The one with the
Ao mambushi
Blue mambushi
White mambushi
white mambushi
It'll come off.
It won't shrink
It won't shrink there
The flower I made
That's the important part. Fujimoto-san's last video.
Let's go.Let's go.
Here's Fujimoto.
I'm sure he's screwed up somewhere else.
Come on, Dad.
Fujimoto's cute.
You'll be happy. I'll be happy.
They step up to each other.
You're off, and they're pushing each other away.
The distance between us can't get any closer
I can't stop, I can't stop
I'm chasing after you, love
me
Hello, Izumi!
I'm Minato, and this time I'd like to sing "O" three times in the intro.
I'd like you to give me two colors of the buttons for each of the three times the letter O is used in the intro.
I'm thinking it would be nice if you could give them a combination of purple and red, pink and green, blue and yellow, and so on.
The lyrics are blue with the eyes of the sea.
I'm doing this kind of coloring, and I'd be happy if you could give me a heart of red in love.
I'd like to see a button with two colors here, blue and green, if possible.
I would like to have a firework with a name like "Senrin" when I pedal this bicycle.
I think there is a firework with a bicycle-like name
If you can, please join us!
If you can't make it, you can make a firework that looks like a bicycle.
I'll be so happy!
I'd like to have a red lantern with red as the main color.
If there is a small red lantern with red eyes, please give me a little bit of it.
And the ghosts here are marked with nicotine.
It would be nice if you could help us.
That's right.Yes, it is.
Who thought of this?
Did anyone think of this?
Red.
High school student.
Please.
Go on.
Then go to the 1st chorus.
Before the chorus, at the yi-yao part, please let off a big blue round firework with a bang.
Yes, sir.
I want to shoot a big firework before the chorus.
Yes, please.
Then, here, there will be some sweat after the fireworks get wet and dry, and I think it would be cute if you could shoot green, red, purple and gold fireworks at this timing.
And now, to the fireworks about to go off...
I'm sorry, but I'd like to ask you to shoot off one of my fireworks.
Make it stand out.
Failed.
It's not so bad down there.
Next, here's the part where you hold your head in your hands... you did a good job of making the batten fireworks.
I don't know if it's successful or not, but I think we can do it here.
You can do it!
I'd like you to make a conspicuous shot here again.
Please.
Who thought of this?
I did.
The leader this time.
Please.
The leader this time.The leader this time.
Please, please, please.
We're going into the second chorus.
This is the same as the first chorus.
If possible, I'd like you to change the color of the "wet and dry" part here to a different color than before.
And the heart after that is also the same.
From Swissillow
From Swiss-row to Swiss-row
How many times do you want the flowers to go up from here?
I'd like to see a sparkling firework here.
And then the numbers will be overlapped on the four lines of line 3, which will never happen again.
I'd be happy if there are two or three or something to go with them.
And from here on, it will be a little quieter.
If it's possible, I'd like to use this "fresh flower field" like this.
I'd like to do it like this.
I'd like you to put something like that on it.
I'd like you to put it on.
I'd like you to add the fireworks that Mr. Fujimoto made before the last chorus.
That's the important part, isn't it?
This is the most important part, and it's up to Mr. Fujimoto, so please let them go up here.
And then the last chorus, I'd like to see you do a big, colorful, boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom boom.
I want you to raise it.
I want them to be powerful.
And colorful fireworks with a bang!
A lot of them.
Yes, a lot of fireworks.
And at the second turn, I'd like another big firework, this time gold.
Boom, boom, boom, gold!Boom, boom, boom, boom, gold.
And then there's a part at the end where the outro goes "oh"...
Look at this.
LOL.
It's a little bit like this, but with a lot of hope.
LOL!
The last part is the best part.
LOL.
I'm looking forward to it.
Mr. Izumi, as far as it's feasible.
I'm counting on you.
Laughs
Music
Please subscribe to our channel.